A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, North Korea Program FA1776
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Northeast Asia Cooperative Security Project, 1968-2020; 1; 52.5 Cubic Feet 138 document boxes: 137 letter boxes and 1 legal box
  - Korea relations and politics, 2010-2011 (Box 102, Folder 531-533)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 103, Folder 534-535)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 103, Folder 536-537)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2011 (Box 103, Folder 538)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2011 (Box 104, Folder 539-540)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 104, Folder 541-542)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 105, Folder 543-544)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 105, Folder 545-546)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 547-548)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 549)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 550)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2011 (Box 107, Folder 551-552)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 107, Folder 553-554)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2012 (Box 107, Folder 555)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2012 (Box 108, Folder 556-557)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 108, Folder 558-560)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 109, Folder 561-564)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2012 (Box 109, Folder 565)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2009-2012 (Box 110, Folder 566)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 110, Folder 567-568)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 110, Folder 569-570)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 111, Folder 571-572)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 111, Folder 573-574)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 111, Folder 575-576)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012 (Box 112, Folder 577)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2012-2013 (Box 112, Folder 578-580)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 113, Folder 581-583)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2013 (Box 113, Folder 584-585)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2013 (Box 114, Folder 586-587)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 114, Folder 588-590)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2013 (Box 115, Folder 591-593)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 115, Folder 594-595)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 116, Folder 596)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 116, Folder 597-598)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 116, Folder 599-600)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 116, Folder 601)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 117, Folder 602)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 117, Folder 603-604)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 117, Folder 605)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 117, Folder 606)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 118, Folder 607-608)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 118, Folder 609)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2015 (Box 118, Folder 610)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 119, Folder 611-612)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 119, Folder 613-615)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 120, Folder 616-617)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 120, Folder 618-619)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 121, Folder 620-621)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 121, Folder 622-623)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 121, Folder 624-625)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 121, Folder 626)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 122, Folder 627-628)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 122, Folder 629-631)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 123, Folder 632-633)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2016 (Box 123, Folder 634-635)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 123, Folder 636-637)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 124, Folder 638-639)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 124, Folder 640-642)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 125, Folder 643-645)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2017 (Box 125, Folder 646-647)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2017 (Box 126, Folder 648)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 126, Folder 649-651)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 1, 2017 (Box 126, Folder 652)
  - Korea relations and politics, part 2, 2017 (Box 127, Folder 653-654)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 127, Folder 655-657)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2017 (Box 128, Folder 658-660)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 128, Folder 661-663)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 129, Folder 664-665)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 129, Folder 666-667)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 130, Folder 668-669)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2018 (Box 130, Folder 670-671)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 130, Folder 672-673)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 131, Folder 674-675)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 131, Folder 676-677)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 131, Folder 678)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 132, Folder 679-680)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 132, Folder 681-682)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 132, Folder 683)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 132, Folder 684)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 685)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 686-687)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 688)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019 (Box 133, Folder 689)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019-2020 (Box 134, Folder 690)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2019-2020 (Box 134, Folder 691)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2020 (Box 134, Folder 692)
  - Korea relations and politics, 2020 (Box 134, Folder 693)
  - North Korea statements, 1994-2019 (Box 135, Folder 694)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Grant proposals, 2005-2009 (Box 135, Folder 695-696)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Grant proposals, part 1, 1996-2003 (Box 135, Folder 697-698)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Grant proposals, part 2, 2001-2005 (Box 136, Folder 699)
  - Carnegie Corporation - Grant proposals, 2005-2019 (Box 136, Folder 700-703)
  - Ploughshares Fund - Grant proposals, 1999-2014 (Box 137, Folder 704-706)
  - Korea Foundation - Grant proposals, 2006-2015 (Box 137, Folder 707)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Grant proposals, 2008 (Box 137, Folder 708)
  - The Atlantic Philanthropies, 2003-2004 (Box 138, Folder 709)
  - Asia Pacific Peace Foundation, 1996-1997 (Box 138, Folder 710)